<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="Joke">
		<item>
			Lemon juice added to a mug of water can be used as a conditioner for very oily hair.
		</item>
		<item>
			Use conditioner regularly if you have colored your hair as chemical dyes make hair dry and frizzy.
		</item>
		<item>
			To minimize hair loss during brushing use a hair brush with ball-tipped bristles and avoid combing wet hair.
		</item>
		<item>
			Washing hair with very hot water can make it look dull because it strips off the natural oil film that gives shine to hair.
		</item>
		<item>
			Very tightly pulled hairstyles tug at the root of your hair and weaken it. Keep the style relaxed to avoid hair damage.
		</item>
		<item>
			One round of thorough shampooing is enough to clean your hair. Repeating the process is a waste of time, effort and of course shampoo.
		</item>
		<item>
			To get rid of split ends, get a trim at least every six weeks.
		</item>
		<item>
			Use shampoo with ingredients that include sunscreen and moisturizing cream if your hair is extremely dry.
		</item>
		<item>
			Color treated hair is more prone to damage caused by extended sun exposure. Use a hat to protect your hair.
		</item>
		<item>
			Thoroughly wet your hair before plunging into the swimming pool to protect it from damage caused by chlorinated pool water.
		</item>
		<item>
			Avoid plucking hair to remove gray hair. It won`t cause more gray hair, but can damage your hair root.
		</item>
		<item>
			After applying hair conditioner rinse your hair with cold water as hot water will strip off the conditioning agent.
		</item>
		<item>
			If you frequently use a blow-dryer, use a conditioner regularly as it can decrease hair damage caused by blow-drying.
		</item>
		<item>
			For lustrous hair, massage your scalp with warm coconut oil, wrap your hair with a hot towel for about fifteen minutes and then shampoo.
		</item>
		<item>
			Make sure that your diet has adequate amount of protein if you are fighting hair fall.
		</item>
		<item>
			Head massage once a month with a mix of coconut, castor, olive and almond oil is great to nourish dry hair.
		</item>
		<item>
			When coloring gray hair opt for a color close to your own hair color for a natural look and minimum appearance of roots.
		</item>
		<item>
			Regular use of a protein rich conditioner can repair split ends and hair damage caused by excessive styling.
		</item>
		<item>
			Regular gentle head massage promotes blood flow to hair follicles and can help reduce hair fall.
		</item>
		<item>
			Homemade conditioner for dry hair: mix half cup yogurt with one egg white and apply for thirty minutes.
		</item>
		<item>
			Lemon juice added to a mug of water can be used as a conditioner for very oily hair.
		</item>
		<item>
			Rinse your mouth after having citrus fruits and lemon as citric acid in these fruits can erode tooth enamel.
		</item>
		<item>
			Put frozen tea bags on closed eyes for 20 minutes three times a week to reduce dark circles and puffiness.
		</item>
		<item>
			Groomed eyebrows are a must for a neat and smart look. But avoid pencil thin or high arches as they look unnatural.
		</item>
		<item>
			Even when you are not wearing any eye make up, curl your eyelashes to make your eyes look larger and brighter.
		</item>
		<item>
			If you have dark circles, apply an under eye gel containing a lightening ingredient like vitamin C and a collagen-builder like retinal.
		</item>
		<item>
			Wear sunglasses if you spend a lot of time outdoors. It protects the skin around your eyes and also helps you avoid squinting.
		</item>
		<item>
			Dry flaky lips appear thin and give you an aged look. Apply lip balm generously for full and young looking lips.
		</item>
		<item>
			Use a lip balm containing shea butter to help your lips heal faster.
		</item>
		<item>
			If you have brittle nails, rub a waxy lip balm on them to make them soft.
		</item>
		<item>
			Quick nail care at home: remove nail polish, clean nails with lemon juice and massage cuticles with lip balm.
		</item>
		<item>
			Exposing your hands to soap and water for long periods can make nails split and break. Applying thick moisturizer may help.
		</item>
		<item>
			Avoid using harsh cleansers even if you have oily skin. Something that makes your skin feel tight and dry is not right for it.
		</item>
		<item>
			Cleanse your face before going to bed even if you have been indoors and applied no makeup to get rid of bacteria,dead cells and oil.
		</item>
		<item>
			Keep your skincare regime simple. Avoid using too many products as the ingredients could react and irritate your skin.
		</item>
		<item>
			Frequent and vigorous cleansing can irritate your skin and make acne worse. Wash acne-prone skin twice daily with a mild soap and warm water.
		</item>
		<item>
			Do not wash your face more than twice a day as excessive cleansing strips off the protective layer that keeps skin soft and healthy.
		</item>
		<item>
			A mix of sandalwood and almond paste is a very effective remedy for removing sun tan and is also soothing for the skin.
		</item>
		<item>
			For super soft skin massage your body with oil before getting into the shower. Then exfoliate with a mild scrub.
		</item>
		<item>
			A glass of carrot juice is loaded with vitamins that are great for your skin and has fewer calories than fruit juices.
		</item>
		<item>
			If you have sensitive skin, prefer a fragrance free moisturizer as additives used for fragrance can irritate your skin.
		</item>
		<item>
			Scrubbing is good for acne prone skin but only when done very gently. Harsh scrubbing can worsen acne by aggravating inflammation.
		</item>
		<item>
			Never exert pressure on the face while massaging it. Facial massage should always be done with a light, feathery touch of fingers.
		</item>
		<item>
			Applying a pack made of tomato pulp and lemon juice can reduce acne as it has antibacterial properties.
		</item>
		<item>
			To lighten black spots left by acne apply sandalwood paste mixed with rose water. Leave on for 30 minutes and wash.
		</item>
		<item>
			Adequate sleep is a must for youthful skin. Skin repairing hormones are released while you sleep.
		</item>
		<item>
			Your skin needs special care after mid-twenties as skin renewal slows down. Good diet and moisturizing well are most important.
		</item>
		<item>
			It`s a good idea to use a separate small towel for your face and wash it more often to keep skin free of pimples.
		</item>
		<item>
			Reduce the redness around a recently burst pimple by applying ice for five to ten minutes.
		</item>
		<item>
			Stress is a major reason for dull looking skin.Yoga or meditation can be your key to looking your best everyday.
		</item>
		<item>
			Gram flour mixed with milk, lemon juice and turmeric powder is an excellent cleanser to remove makeup and dirt.
		</item>
		<item>
			Blackheads and whiteheads are caused by clogged pores. Applying a retinol containing cream can help clear them off.
		</item>
		<item>
			Avoid using antibacterial soap on your face on a daily basis as most of them are too harsh for your skin.
		</item>
		<item>
			Apply a paste of coconut milk and sandalwood powder on your face. It removes dead skin and makes your skin soft and glowing.
		</item>
		<item>
			Oily skin also needs moisturizer. But you need to use products that are water based and non comedogenic.
		</item>
		<item>
			If you have sensitive skin avoid using fruit based face scrubs. Go for scrubs with synthetic beads which are more uniform and gentle.
		</item>
		<item>
			If you have normal to dry skin, you can use extra virgin olive oil as a moisturizer at night to make your skin super soft.
		</item>
		<item>
			Keep hair away from your face if you are prone to acne. Constant contact with hair irritates skin and can cause breakouts.
		</item>
		<item>
			Avoid squeezing pimples as it pushes infected material deeper into your skin leading to more zits.
		</item>
		<item>
			Rosewater works as an excellent gentle toner for sensitive skin.
		</item>
		<item>
			To lighten sun tan mix equal amounts of potato juice and lemon juice, apply on affected area for fifteen minutes and wash off.
		</item>
		<item>
			Winter sun is milder but can still damage your skin. Apply ample sunscreen before you enjoy the sunshine.
		</item>
		<item>
			Coconut oil is an excellent body moisturizer. It has good amounts of Vitamin E which is excellent for the skin.
		</item>
		<item>
			Baby shampoo can be used for removing heavy makeup. It will do all the cleansing and won`t irritate your skin and eyes.
		</item>
		<item>
			To reduce skin oiliness, apply a mixture of one tsp of honey with one tsp of lemon juice and egg white. Wash off after 20 minutes.
		</item>
		<item>
			For a glowing complexion, apply a face pack of saffron, sandalwood paste and turmeric mixed in yogurt or milk.
		</item>
		<item>
			To make a natural age-defying face pack: mix 1 egg yolk, 1 tablespoon of honey, 1 tablespoon of plain yogurt,and half teaspoon of olive oil.
		</item>
		<item>
			Age shows not only on face but also on the skin of your hands and feet. Moisturize them regularly to keep them wrinkle free.
		</item>
		<item>
			The skin on your neck and hands tells your age. Anti-ageing treatments should also focus on these areas for a truly younger appearance.
		</item>
		<item>
			Use a strong scrub such as one with apricot kernels for exfoliating hands, feet and back to get rid of dead skin cells.
		</item>
		<item>
			Rub an ice cube over your face before applying foundation. This closes your pores and prevents them from getting clogged with makeup.
		</item>
		<item>
			Silicone containing foundations are great for mature skin as they glide smoothly without settling in fine lines and wrinkles.
		</item>
		<item>
			Avoid applying lipstick on dry chapped lips. Moisturize and gently remove flakes to make your lipstick look better.
		</item>
		<item>
			To make thin lips appear full dab some lip gloss in the center of your lower lip after applying lipstick.
		</item>
		<item>
			Blend a light colored highlighter with your eye shadow to create the impression of large beautiful eyes.
		</item>
		<item>
			A quick dab of compressed powder can make an oily and tired face look fresh in seconds.
		</item>
		<item>
			Do not try to match your lip and nail colors with your dress. Go for colors that complement your skin tone and do not clash with the dress.
		</item>
		<item>
			To prevent mascara from flaking or smudging, run an eyelash brush through lashes to remove clumpy mascara build-up.
		</item>
		<item>
			Use a good moisturiser for a clean, fresh look and some tinted blush on cheeks to add instant colour to the face.
		</item>
		<item>
			Replace your eye liner and mascara every three months to minimize the chances of eye infection.
		</item>
		<item>
			Never apply foundation lighter than your actual skin color as it will make your makeup look very unnatural.
		</item>
		<item>
			If you do not have time for facial before party then apply an egg white mask and rub an ice cube on your face before putting makeup.
		</item>
		<item>
			Wash your makeup brushes with some shampoo to keep them bacteria free and hence healthy for your skin.
		</item>
		<item>
			For a glamorous look, choose a bright colored nail polish that compliments your skin tone.
		</item>
		<item>
			For a radiant but natural look, apply body shimmer after you have applied moisturizer. This also makes the shimmer set better.
		</item>
		<item>
			Very dark lipstick color can make your lips thin and aged. For plump lips use a lip-liner and fill with a slightly lighter shade.
		</item>
		<item>
			Thick foundation can make wrinkles very prominent. Light foundation dabbed with a sponge gives a smoother look.
		</item>
		<item>
			When applying anti-aging creams pay maximum attention to areas around the mouth, eyes and neck as they are most prone to wrinkles.
		</item>
		<item>
			Clever makeup should highlight your best feature. Use bold lipstick on shapely lips or eyeliner to emphasize beautiful eyes.
		</item>
		<item>
			If you have applied a bright colored lipstick, use neutral colors on your cheek and eyes for a sophisticated look.
		</item>
		<item>
			Applying nail polish in a hurry? Use a shimmer polish as imperfections in its application will be much less visible.
		</item>
		<item>
			For an extra glamorous evening look apply a shimmer lotion to apt places on your body such as the collar bones.
		</item>
		<item>
			Use products that match your skin type—hydrating formulas for dry skin, water-based for oily skin and hypoallergenic for sensitive skin.
		</item>
		<item>
			If your skin is prone to acne, go for powder based cosmetics instead of cream based ones.
		</item>
		<item>
			For an evening party in dim lights, put some gold dust over your lipstick to give your lips an attractive look.
		</item>
		<item>
			Apply makeup with clean fingertips only as far as possible. Brushes and applicators frequently contain germs that can irritate skin.
		</item>
		<item>
			Gentle exfoliation and deep moisturizing before applying makeup is great because it gives a more fresh and clean look.
		</item>
		<item>
			Always apply makeup with good quality brushes for a clean and professional look.
		</item>
		<item>
			Use makeup to highlight your best features and not to hide imperfections. Downplay the less perfect ones with subtle makeup.
		</item>
		<item>
			Protect your cosmetics from excess light and heat as high temperature will destroy the preservatives that keep the product bacteria free.
		</item>
	</string-array>
</resources>

